(Penny:)I didn't have any quarters.
(Penny:)So I've been sneaking stuff
into other people's loads all day.
(Penny:)If I tell you something,
you promise not to tell anybody?
(Leonard:)Doesn't matter what I say,
you're gonna tell me anyway.
Wha?... That is not true.
(Penny:)Bernadette wants a prenup.
(Leonard:)Wow.
(Leonard:)That's rough.
(Penny:)If I became a famous movie star
and we got married...
(Penny:)- ...you wouldn't sign a prenup?
- Heh, absolutely not.
If I'm gonna be at home
with the kids...
(Leonard:)...while you're on location
cheating on me with Ryan Gosling...
(Leonard:)...then Leonard gots to get paid.
So do you think about us
getting married?
I think about a Iot of things.
(Penny:)I think about us getting married,
about us breaking up.
(Penny:)Once in a while, I think about how I didn't
Ieave a note on that Mercedes I dinged...
(Penny:)...but then I have a glass of wine
and it passes.
(Leonard:)Joke all you want,
but you think about it.
(Penny:)Well, tell you one thing, if I ever do
get married, no Klingon invitations.